你知道谁长得好看吗？
Do you know who looks good?
¿Sabes quién tiene pinta?
我简直要疯了，因为我踩到了 Gordi 的 tarascoro！
I'm going crazy that I'm stepping on Gordi's tarascoro!
¡Me vuelvo loco de que le pise un tarascoro a Gordi!
吓到我了！
It scared me!
¡Me asustó!
写到一半时，我用 tarascoro 打了 Gordi，他怀孕了！
Halfway through the note I hit Gordi with a tarascoro and he got pregnant!
¡Mitad de la nota le clavo un tarascoro a Gordi y le saca preñique!
我要疯了！
I'm going crazy!
¡Me vuelvo loco!
别去吃它！
Don't go eat it!
¡No te vayas a comer!
足球的新篇章，Choco 比赛......
A new chapter of football, the Choco match...
Un nuevo capítulo de fútbol, el partido de Choco...
我是 Alcio，我是 Oficini，我是 Accordini。
I am Alcio, I am Oficini, I am Accordini.
Yo soy Alcio, yo soy Oficini, yo soy Accordini.
让我们看看，国际米兰。
Let's see, Inter.
Vamos a ver, al Inter.
佛罗伦萨。
Fiorentina.
La Fiorentina.
游览城市并采访谁。
Tour the city and interview who.
Recorrer la ciudad y entrevistar a quién.
劳塔罗·马丁内斯，公牛队，国际米兰队长。
To Lautaro Martínez, the Bull, the captain of Inter Milan.
A Lautaro Martínez, el Toro, el capitán del Inter de Milano.
这不是我的吗？
Isn't this mine?
¿Esto no es mío?
伙计，我有一个主意。
Dude, I have an idea.
Amigo, tengo una idea.
如果我们拜访世界各地的朋友怎么办？
What if we visit friends around the world?
¿Y si visitamos amigos por el mundo?
如果我们吃世界各地的食物怎么办？
What if we eat food around the world?
¿Y si comemos comida por el mundo?
如果我们把它命名为 Fugón 会怎么样？
What if we name it Fugón?
¿Y si le ponemos el nombre Fugón?
我认为这是一个好主意。
I think it's an excellent idea.
Me parece una excelente idea.
回声！
ECHO!
烤架怎么样？
How is it with the grill?
¿Cómo está con el asador?
非常好。
Very good.
Muy bien.
吐？
Spit?
¿Asador?
吐。
Spit.
Asador.
你看起来不错。
You look good.
Tenés pinta.
该俱乐部可容纳 70 人。
The club for 70 people.
El club para 70 personas.
哦真的吗？
Oh really?
¿En serio?
你有油漆吗？
Do you have paint?
¿Tenés pintado?
我已经烧了。
I have burnt.
Tengo quemado.
哦真的吗？
Oh really?
¿En serio?
不，是手。
No, the hands.
No, las manos.
没关系，没关系。
It's okay, it's okay.
Está bien, está bien.
我有视频所以...
I have video so...
Tengo video para que...
我们还好吗？
We're ok?
¿Estamos bien?
我快疯了，你这个白痴，我认识这个人这么久了，他刚刚
I'm losing my mind, you idiot, I've known the man for so long when he just
Me estoy quedando pelado boludo, yo lo conozco al señor de tantísimo tiempo cuando recién
它从一档开始。
It started in first gear.
Arrancaba en primera.
你会说意大利语吗？
Do you speak Italian?
¿Parla italiano?
不。
No.
我不会说意大利语，但尝试一下。
I don't speak Italian and try, try a little.
Yo no parlo italiano e intentare, intentare un poquitino.
不，你必须整天听它，而不是忍受它。
No, you have to listen to it all day, without enduring it.
No, tenes que escucharlo todo el dia, sin soportar.
看来我女儿开始上学时就想说意大利语。
It seems like my daughter wanted to speak Italian when she started school.
Parece mi hija cuando arrancó la escuela que quería hablar italiano.
不，这完全是疯了。
No, it's totally crazy.
No, totalmente es una locura.
嘿，当你到达时这里的语言是更容易学还是更复杂？
Hey, and is the language here easier to learn when you arrived or complicated?
Che, ¿y el idioma acá más fácil para aprender cuando llegaste o complicado?
瞧，我上了三节课……
Look, I took three classes...
Mirá, hice tres clases...
第三节课我让老师站着。
In the third class I left the teacher standing.
A la tercera clase dejé plantada a la profe.
下面，老师正在上英语课。
Below, the teacher was giving a lesson in English.
Abajo, la profesora daba lección en inglés.
所以我不会说英语。
So I don't speak English.
Entonces yo no hablo inglés.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我午睡了，五点钟老师就带我来了。
I slept at naps, at five o'clock the teacher took me.
Dormía a la siesta, a las cinco llevaba la profe.
那时我还没有孩子，所以这是我的午睡。
At that time I didn't have children so it was my nap.
En ese momento no tenía hijos así que la siesta mía.
怎么一切都变了，对吧？
How everything changed, right?
Como cambió todo, ¿no?
它改变了，对吗？
It changed, right?
¿Cambió, no?
它改变了很多。
It changed a lot.
Cambió muchísimo.
不再了。
Anymore.
Nunca más.
六个月后...
After six months...
A los seis meses...
我在俱乐部做出了承诺，显然俱乐部告诉我，你必须说意大利语。
I had made a promise at the club, that obviously the club told me, you have to speak Italian.
Había hecho una promesa en el club, que obviamente en el club me decían, tenés que hablar italiano.
我说，他付钱给我玩、说话，我告诉他。
I said, he pays me for playing, for talking, I told him.
Yo decía, a mí me paga por jugando, por hablar, le decía yo.
这句话一直持续到十二月而且效果很好
and well that sentence lasts until December and it does it quite well
y bueno esa frase dura hasta diciembre y bastante bien lo hace
现在让我们参观一下博物馆。
Now let's go through the museum.
Ahora vamos a pasar por el museo.
我不想冒险。
I didn't want to risk it.
No me quería arriesgar.
然后是圣诞节前一天的第一个音符。
and then the first note the day before Christmas.
y después la primera nota el día antes de Navidad.
一旦你说意大利语，你就必须继续。
Once you speak Italian, you have to continue.
A partir de una vez que habla italiano, hay que seguir.
我们开始了解Gensomina，一个地方
We come to know Gensomina, a place
Venimos a conocer Gensomina, un lugar
典型的米兰糕点，其中的明星是开心果。
of typical Milanese pastries and where the star is the pistachio.
de pastelería típica milanesa y donde la vedete es el pistache.
开心果 我很高兴尝试意大利菜，我不想放弃任何东西，但我们现在要展示的产品非常棒
the pistachio I am very excited to try Italian food I don't want to give anything away but they make a product that we are now going to present that is tremendous
el pistachio estoy muy emocionado por probar comida italiana no quiero adelantar nada pero hacen un producto que ahora lo vamos a presentar que es tremendo
你要把它介绍给我吗？
Are you going to introduce it to me?
¿Me lo vas a presentar vos?
是的，请。
Yes please.
Sí, por favor.
你要告诉我一切吗？
Are you going to tell me everything?
¿Me lo vas a informar todo?
是的，让我们看看。
Yes, let's see.
Sí, vamos a ver.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
¿Cómo es tu nombre?
你的名字。
Your name.
Tu nombre.
费德里科.
Federico.
费德里科！
¡Federico!
我们三个人！
All three of us!
¡Los tres de nosotros!
难以置信，爸爸！
Incredible, dad!
¡Increíble, papá!
奇妙！
Marvelous!
¡Maravilloso!
儿子，你点了巧克力吗？
Did you order a chocolate, son?
¿Vos te pediste una chocolatada, hijo?
我问自己一个...
I asked myself for a...
Yo me pedí un...
一杯拿铁玛奇朵，我发誓我对喝它感到抱歉，因为它有一个美丽的名字，看看这个，看看这是什么
a latte macchiato that I swear I feel sorry for drinking it because it has a beautiful name, look at this, look at what this is
un latte macchiato que te juro que me da pena tomarlo porque está el nombre hermoso mira esto, mira lo que es esto
很明显，这是一款千年饮品，千年饮品。
It is very clear that it is a millennial drink, a thousand-year-old drink.
Está clarísimo que es bebida de millennial, bebida de mil años.
他康复了。
He recovered.
Recubeneció.
多么美妙啊。
How wonderful.
Qué maravilla.
他康复了。
He recovered.
Recubeneció.
有多强，对吧？
How strong, right?
Qué fuerte, ¿no?
让我们看看，我可以尝试一下吗？
Let's see, can I try it?
A ver, ¿lo puedo probar?
不。
No.
到帕皮罗拉。
to the papirola.
a la papirola.
这有点违背现代足球的运作方式，明白吗？
That goes somewhat against how modern football works, see?
Eso va medio en contra de cómo funciona el fútbol moderno, ¿viste?
球员们从一个俱乐部跳到另一个俱乐部。
That the players jump from club to club.
Que los jugadores van saltando de club en club.
在这件事发生之前，你会看到，有一名球员被推荐到俱乐部。
And before it happened, you saw, that there was a player who was referred to a club.
Y antes pasaba, viste, que había un jugador que quedaba referenciado a un club.
在我看来，你的工作有点像那样。
And it seems to me that you work a little like that.
Y vos me parece que funcionas un poco así.
找到自己在世界上的位置是一件非常重要的事情。
There is something very about having found your place in the world.
Hay una cosa muy de haber encontrado medio tu lugar en el mundo.
并感觉，如果我在这里很好，为什么我要去别的地方呢？
and feel that, why am I going to go somewhere else if I'm fine here?
y sentir que, ¿para qué me voy a ir a otro lado si estoy bien acá?
好吧，这也很困难，因为除了我们到达这里的第一刻之外，我们总是......
And well, it's also difficult because beyond the fact that the first moment we get here we always...
Y bueno, es difícil también porque más allá de que el primer momento que llegamos acá siempre nos...
他们对我们很好，我的一切都进展顺利。
They have treated us well and things have always gone well for me.
Nos han tratado bien y siempre me ha ido bien.
今天我是一支非常大的球队的队长。
And today I am the captain of a very big team.
Y hoy soy el capitán de un equipo muy grande.
在世界范围内，自从我到达以来的过去几年里，我们赢得了许多冠军。
worldwide and in the last few years since I arrived we have won many titles.
a nivel mundial y en los últimos años desde que llegué yo hemos ganado muchos títulos.
我们已经两次进入欧冠决赛，我们也进入了欧罗巴联赛决赛。
We have reached two Champions League finals, we have reached the Europa League final.
Hemos llegado a dos finales de Champions, hemos llegado a la final de Europa League.
如果你开始分析一切，显然很难停下来。
If you start to analyze everything, it is obviously difficult to step aside.
Si vos te ponés a analizar todo obviamente es difícil dar un paso al costado.
这是非常困难的。
It's very difficult.
Es muy difícil.
去某个地方他们会为您提供什么？
What are they going to offer you to go somewhere?
¿Qué te van a ofrecer para irte a un lugar?
你哪里会变得更好？
Where are you going to be better?
¿Dónde vas a estar mejor?
我总是优先考虑体育，而不是经济。
I always prioritized sports, not economics.
Yo siempre prioricé siempre lo deportivo, no lo económico.
因为如果经济的话，我已经收到了报价。
Because if it were economical, I have had offers.
Porque si fuese por lo económico, he tenido ofertas.
也很难说不，但我总是选择熟悉的、经济的、让我快乐、满足的地方。
It was also difficult to say no, but I always went for what was familiar, for what was economic, where I was happy, where I was content.
que era difícil también decir que no, pero siempre fui por lo familiar, por lo económico, por donde yo estaba feliz, donde estaba contento.
我感觉很舒服的地方，但我不称其为舒适区，因为
where I felt comfortable and I didn't call it a comfort zone because
donde me sentía cómodo y no lo llamó zona de confort porque
我每天都在努力提高自己，就像我在赛车比赛中所做的那样。
Every day I try to improve myself, as I did in Racing.
Todos los días yo trato de superarme, como lo hacía en Racing.
我喜欢有食欲。
I like appetite.
Me gusta el apetito.
事实是，当你赢得冠军时，你想继续获胜。
The truth is that when you win a title, you want to keep winning.
La verdad es que cuando uno gana título, quiere seguir ganando.
一个人必须拥有的精神和饥饿，同样的事情也会发生
the spirit and the hunger that one has to have, the same thing happens
el espíritu y el hambre que uno tiene que tener, lo mismo pasa
在其他工作中以及如果您得到晋升。
in other jobs and if you get promoted.
en otros trabajos y si te ascienden.
就是这样。
It's about that.
Se trata de eso.
今天我在这里过得很好，很开心。
Today I am very well here, happy.
Yo hoy estoy muy bien acá, feliz.
我的家人在这里。
My family is here.
Mi familia está acá.
就像我告诉过你的，我们有一家餐厅。
Like I told you, we have a restaurant.
Como te digo, tenemos un restaurante.
我的孩子们开始上学了。
My children started school.
Mis hijos arrancaron el colegio.
也没什么，我们很高兴。
And nothing, we are happy.
Y nada, estamos felices.
我在这里续签了合同。
I renewed the contract here.
Renové el contrato acá.
在体育水平上。
At a sporting level.
A nivel deportivo.
你错过了国际米兰的欧冠联赛吗？
Are you missing the Champions League with Inter?
¿Te falta la Champions con el Inter?
另一个梦想是有一天重返竞技队和解放者队。
And the other dream out there is to one day return to Racing and the Libertadores.
Y el otro sueño por ahí es volver un día a Racing y la Libertadores.
是的，毫无疑问。
Yes, without a doubt.
Sí, sin duda.
毫无疑问，今天的欧冠联赛对我来说是一种痴迷。
Without a doubt, the Champions League is an obsession for me today.
Sin duda que la Champions para mí hoy es una obsesión.
我们是如此接近，但我们却做不到。
We were so close and we couldn't do it.
Estuvimos tan cerca y no lo pudimos lograr.
是从 City 来的吧？
The one from City, right?
La del City, ¿no?
是的，这比曼城、巴黎圣日耳曼这支新球队更重要。
Yes, more than anything that of City, that of PSG, the new party.
Sí, más que nada la del City, la del PSG, el nuevo partido.
我已经谈过了，很难评论那天晚上发生的事情，但是......
I already talked about it and it's difficult to comment on what happened that night, but...
Ya lo hablé y es difícil de comentar lo que pasó esa noche, pero...
对于城市城市，我们在那里他们可能是最受欢迎的。
With City City we were there where they were perhaps favorites.
con el City City estuvimos ahí donde ellos eran favoritos quizás.
那一刻我们平静地到达了。
At that moment we arrived calmly.
En ese momento llegábamos nosotros como tranquilos.
但你们派上了用场。
But you guys came in handy.
Pero venían bien ustedes.
他们是夺冠热门，所以也许这是一场我们打得更轻松、更平静的比赛。
And they arrived as the favorites, so perhaps it was a game that we played more relaxed, calmer.
Y ellos llegaban como los favoritos, entonces quizás fue un partido que jugamos más relajado, más tranquilo.
我们很亲密，然后很明显，我每天都对我的妻子
We were close and then yes obviously to my wife every day
estuvimos cerca y después sí obviamente a mi mujer todos los días
回到赛车，回到赛车，但为什么呢？
go back to Racing, go back to Racing, but why?
volver a Racing, volver a Racing, pero ¿por qué?
这是我的一个梦想，也许也是我对家人许下的回归的承诺
It's a dream that I have, maybe a promise that I also made to my family to return to
Es un sueño que tengo, una promesa quizá que le hice a mi familia también de volver a
去俱乐部，我也一直给我的孩子们穿这件球衣，因为
to the club and I also wear the shirt to my children all the time because
al club y a mis hijos también le pongo la camiseta todo el tiempo porque
我希望他们也能看到足球对我们意味着什么。
I would love for them to also see what football means to us.
Me encantaría que ellos vean también lo que significa el fútbol para nosotros.
以及赛车对我生活的意义，因为它改变了我的生活。
and what Racing means in my life because beyond everything it has changed my life.
y lo que significa Racing en mi vida porque más allá de todo me ha cambiado la vida.
它给了我成为一名职业选手的机会，我将永远感激所有人。
It has given me the opportunity to be a professional player and I will be forever grateful to all the people.
Me ha dado la oportunidad de ser jugador profesional y le estaré agradecido por vida a toda la gente.
我在这儿，跟着你。
I'm here, follow you.
Ya estoy yo, seguí vos.
现在有了小露台，听我说。
Now with the little terrace, listen to me.
Ya con el terratito, escuchame.
和妻子吵架时哭了。
cries in fight with my wife.
llora en pelea con mi mujer.
因为在比赛中，当然，你会在黎明时看到它。
Because in the games, of course, you see it at dawn.
Porque en los partidos, claro, lo ves a la madrugada.
以及它所赋予的一切的光芒。
And the shine to everything it gives.
Y el brillo a todo lo que da.
如果没有的话，我不明白，小家伙。
If not, I don't see, little one.
Si no, no veo, chiquitito.
哦，瓜皮罗拉！
Oh the guapirola!
¡Oh la guapirola!
哦，里面有开心果，上面。
Oh, it has pistachio inside, on top.
Ah, tiene pistacho adentro, encima.
不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no.
我们来试试吧。
Let's try.
Vamos a probar.
不，是下面的开心果酱。
No, the pistachio sauce below.
No, la salsa de pistachos abajo.
再给我一份吧，太疯狂了。
Give me one more, it's crazy.
Dame una más, es una locura.
你能看到中间的开心果酱吗？
Can you see the pistachio sauce in the middle there?
¿Se llega a ver la salsa de pistacho ahí en el medio?
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
这太疯狂了，是吧？
It's totally crazy, huh?
Es totalmente una locura, ¿eh?
不，孩子。
No, kid.
No, chabón.
这是我一生中最好的事情。
It's the best thing for my life.
Es la mejor cosa para mi vida.
这是巧克力葡萄园。
This is chocolate vineyard.
Esto es viñe al chocolate.
我真的很讨厌开心果。
I really hate the pistachio one.
Le tengo muchísima fea al de pistacho.
就像一颗开心果炸弹。
It's like a pistachio bomb.
Es como una bomba de pistachos.
我们去吃巧克力吧。
Let's go to the chocolate.
Vamos al chocolate.
中间有馅料，上面有一层巧克力……
It has filling in the middle, it has like a layer of chocolate on top and...
Tiene relleno en el medio, tiene arriba como una capa de chocolate y...
这是一份卡纳佩西托。
It's a canapesito.
Es un canapesito.
我对这一点确实有很大的信心。
I do have a lot of faith in this one.
A este sí que le tengo mucha fe.
看，这是开心果奶油，看。
Look, this is a pistachio cream, look.
Mira, esto es una crema de pistachos, mira.
你看还有时间补充和期末吗？
Do you see that there is time to supplement and the final?
¿Ves que hay tiempo de suplementar y la final?
太不可思议了。
It's incredible.
Es increíble.
是的，一对夫妇的角色加倍。
Yes, a couple to double the role.
Sí, una pareja a los dobles del papel.
我又清理了一遍，因为我们还有第三个要尝试，就像......
I cleaned again because we have the third one to try, which is like...
Limpié de nuevo porque tenemos el tercero para probar, que es como...
里面有像糕点师一样的蛋糕。
A cake that has like a pastry chef inside.
Una tarta que tiene como una pastelera dentro.
什么糕点师？
What pastry chef?
¿Qué pastelera?
我对这个？
Me to this one?
¿Yo a este?
我不是 Ligo 的好朋友，但我觉得我必须屈服于这个过程。
I'm not a big friend of Ligo, but I feel like I have to surrender to the process.
No soy muy amigo del Ligo, pero siento que me tengo que entregar al proceso.
戴尔，我爱你……我爱你在我的头发里。
Dale, I love you... I love you in my hair.
Dale, te quiero... te quiero en la canita.
¡罗拉洛？
¿Rorralo?
快点！
Come on!
¡Vamos!
它开始好转。
It started to improve.
Empezó a mejorar.
这是一个古老的国家，这就是我喜欢它的原因。
It's an old country, that's why I liked it.
Es patria de viejo, por eso me gustó a mí.
嗯，一旦你来尝试说价格也很重要，对吧？
Well, it's also important once you come to try to say the prices, right?
Bueno, también es importante una vez que uno viene a probar decir los precios, ¿no?
有几个出来了？
How many came out?
¿Cuántos salieron?
一杯激进的拿铁咖啡。
A radical latte.
Un latte radical.
一个天壤之别。
An abysmal difference.
Una diferencia abismal.
好的。
GOOD.
Bien.
我们有一大杯maquiato拿铁，两欧元。
We have a large maquiato latte, two euros.
Tenemos un latte maquiato grande, dos euros.
好的。
GOOD.
Bien.
你的咖啡？
Your coffee?
¿Tu cafecito?
一点二十。
One twenty.
Uno veinte.
我们有两块巧克力糖果和一颗开心果糖果。
We have the two chocolate bonbons and the pistachio one.
Tenemos los dos bombonsitos de chocolate y el de pistacho.
叫什么名字？
What was the name?
¿Cómo era el nombre?
呃，不能给我。
Uh, I can't give it to me.
Uh, no me la puedo dar.
你向我扔了 200 公斤泥土，足够多了。
You threw 200 kilos of dirt at me, plenty of it.
Me tiraste 200 kilos de tierra, sobravo.
小巧克力，每块两块，每块两欧元。
The little chocolates, two each, two euros each.
Los bombonsitos, dos cada uno, dos euros cada uno.
无花果馅饼最多三个。
The tart with figs up three.
La tartita con higos arriba tres.
还有糕点师。
And pastry chef.
Y pastelera.
那大的呢？
And the big one?
¿Y el grande?
6 欧元大牌是这个地方的明星，绝对是每个人都来尝试的
and the big 6 euros the star of the house which is the big star of the place is exactly what absolutely everyone comes to try
y el grande 6 euros la estrella de la casa que es la gran estrella del lugar es justamente lo que viene a probar absolutamente todo el mundo
好吧，朋友们，我们继续巡演吗？
Well, friends, shall we continue touring?
Bueno, amigos, ¿vamos a seguir recorriendo?
我们对健康的看法是错误的。
We are wrong about our health.
Nos equivocamos de salud.
我们继续游览吧。
Let's continue touring.
Vamos a seguir recorriendo.
你对此有何准备？
How do you prepare for that?
¿Cómo te preparas para eso?
你如何应对世界杯的焦虑？
How do you handle anxiety for a World Cup?
¿Cómo manejas la ansiedad para un mundial?
嗯，不是焦虑，而是……
Well, not anxiety, but...
Bueno, ansiedad no, sino...
带着巨大的渴望，巨大的渴望去准备，以最好的方式到达，因为上一届世界杯来自......
with great desire, great desire to prepare, to arrive in the best way, because the last World Cup comes from...
con muchas ganas, muchas ganas de prepararme, de llegar de la mejor manera, porque la última Copa del Mundo llegue de...
我的脚踝在身体上有点不好，但我没有
physically a little bad in my ankle and that was something I didn't
físicamente un poco mal del tobillo y eso fue algo que no
我不想，我没想到，但我也在注释中说过
that I didn't want, that I didn't expect, but I have also said it in the notes where
que no quería, que no esperaba, pero lo he dicho también en las notas donde
在那里我不得不谈论这个话题，我没有跳过培训课程，我渗透了一整年，甚至
where I had to talk about this topic that I didn't skip a training session, I infiltrated the whole year and even
donde me tocó hablar de este tema que no me saltaba un entrenamiento, me infiltré todo el año y hasta
直到同年我们进入欧洲冠军联赛决赛，他在比赛中脚踝受伤，
Until that same year we reached the Champions League final, he played with an infiltrated ankle,
hasta ese mismo año que llegamos a la final de la Champions, jugaba con el tobillo infiltrado,
直到那一刻我想做手术。
until that moment came when I wanted to have surgery.
hasta que llegó ese momento que quería operarme.
我可以选择对脚踝进行手术，但医生建议我不要这样做。
There was the option of having surgery on my ankle and the doctors recommended that I not do it.
Estaba la opción esa de operarme el tobillo y los médicos me recomendaron no hacerlo.
但到了这个地步，是因为我再也无法忍受痛苦了。
But reaching that point was because I couldn't stand the pain anymore.
Pero el llegar a ese punto era porque ya no aguantaba más el dolor.
他的脚踝没有知觉。
He had no feeling in his ankles.
No tenía sensibilidad en los tobillos.
药物对我没有任何作用，疗法对我也没有任何作用。
The medicine didn't do anything for me, the therapy didn't do anything for me.
La medicina no me hacía nada, la terapia no me hacía nada.
这是我享受比赛、享受当下的方式。
It's my way of living the games, of living the moments.
Es mi forma de vivir los partidos, de vivir los momentos.
这就是为什么我告诉你，今天我正在以最好的方式准备，在身体上努力提高一切。
That's why I tell you that today I am preparing in the best way, physically trying to improve everything.
Por eso te digo que hoy me estoy preparando de la mejor manera, físicamente tratando de mejorar todo.
尝试在最好的条件下到达那一刻。
try to reach that moment in the best conditions.
tratar de llegar a ese momento en las mejores condiciones.
所有使用它并在监狱中生活的人也是如此。
So are all those who use it and live it in prison.
Así todos los que lo blandan y la viven en el penal.
但是嘿，没关系。
But hey, it doesn't matter.
Pero bueno, no importa.
这是一个集体的事情，我们不仅是阿根廷的球迷，我们都是劳塔罗·马丁内斯的球迷。
There was a collective thing, not only were we all fans of Argentina, we were all fans of Lautaro Martínez.
Había una cosa colectiva, no solo éramos todos hinchas de Argentina, éramos todos hinchas de Lautaro Martínez.
人们已经知道这一努力，在我看来，也许这种情况会发生在你身上，期待你所说的下一个......
It was already known about that effort and it seems to me that maybe that happens to you, looking ahead to the next one you say...
ya se sabía de ese esfuerzo y me parece que capaz que te pasa eso, de cara al próximo decís...
现在我想要变得更好，就是这样，准备好了，现象，但我想要变得更好
Now I want to get better, that's it, ready, phenomenon, but I want to get better from
Ahora quiero llegar mejor, ya está, listo, fenómeno, pero quiero llegar mejor desde
显然，这是两项不同的比赛，但对于美洲杯来说，也是在那一刻，那一年。
Obviously they are two different competitions, but for the Copa América also at that moment, that year.
Obviamente son dos competiciones distintas, pero para la Copa América también en ese momento, ese año.
之后我以最好的方式做好了准备。
Afterwards I prepared myself in the best way.
Después me preparé de la mejor manera.
我必须在国际米兰度过一个伟大的赛季，然后成为杯赛上的最佳射手，但出场时间也很少。
I had to have a great season with Inter and then emerge as the top scorer in the Cup, also playing little.
Me tocó hacer una gran temporada con el Inter y después salir goleador de la Copa también jugando poco.
但显然，我们要充分利用机会，然后做好准备。
But obviously taking advantage of the opportunities and then always prepared, obviously.
Pero obviamente aprovechando las oportunidades y después siempre preparado, obviamente.
阿根廷队是最好的球队之一，所以我总是说我们每天都在接受考验。
The Argentine team is among the best, so I always say that every day we take a test to be there.
La selección argentina está en los mejores, entonces siempre digo que todos los días rendimos examen para estar ahí.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
所以我总是这么认为，然后教练的决定就会被接受。
So I always take it that way and then the coach's decisions are accepted.
Así que yo siempre lo tomo de esa manera y después las decisiones del entrenador van aceptadas.
时刻准备着。
Always prepared.
Siempre preparado.
虽然这看起来像个笑话，但我的背已经僵硬了，我们要去米兰的鱼店试试。
Although this may seem like a joke, my back just got stiff and we are going to try Milano's fish shop.
Aunque esto parezca una joda, me acabo de quedar duro la espalda y vamos a probar la pecería de Milano.
Ficha 将展示它。
Ficha is going to present it.
La va a presentar Ficha.
他向我抱怨！
He complained to me!
¡Me quejó!
我看到你的健康状况不佳，而让乔迪尼恢复活力的唯一方法就是去游泳池。
I saw you in poor health and the only way for Jordini to revive is with a pool.
Te vi mal de la salud y la única manera de que Jordini reviva es con una piscina.
我喜欢它，因为他们给你茶角和部分的形状，而且部分是XL号
I love it because they give you the tea angle with the shape of the portion and the portion is XL
Me encanta porque te dan el teangulo con la forma de la porción y la porción es XL
我告诉你一件事，这是普通的，有一个很大的。
I'll tell you something, this is the regular one, there was a large one.
Te voy a decir algo, esta es la regular, había una large.
比这个还大？
Bigger than this?
¿Más grande que esto?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我们折叠 puntini 和便便！
We fold the puntini and poo!
Doblamos la puntini y ¡puuu!
就在那里。
There it is.
Ahí está.
山脉带走你的一切，带走它，带走它
the mountain range takes you everything, take it take it take it
el cordillero te lleva todo, llévalo llévalo llévalo
这个披萨与众不同，因为它更像
This pizza is different because it is like more
es diferente la pizza esta porque es como más
更高、更大、没有质量、没有质量、不是有限的
taller, bigger, has no mass, has no mass, is not finite
más alta, más grandota, no tiene masa, no tiene masa, no es finita
就像……我的祖母就是这样。
It's like... my grandmother has been like that.
Es como... ha sido así mi abuela.
你知道我最喜欢的是披萨。
You know that what I like the most is pizza.
Vos sabés que a mí lo que más me gusta es la pizza.
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
不。
No.
托尼、耐莉是谁？
Who is Nelly, Tony?
¿Quién es Nelly, Tony?
我的祖父母。
My grandparents.
Mis abuelos.
我的祖父母灭霸。
My grandparents Thanos.
Mis abuelos Thanos.
八欧元。
Eight euros.
Ocho euros.
八欧元。
Eight euros.
Ocho euros.
好的。
GOOD.
Bien.
咸，像意大利辣香肠一样咸。
Salty, salty like pepperoni.
Salada, salada como el pepperoni.
在这家比萨饼店的后面，我们有画廊
Behind our backs of this pizzeria we have the gallery
Atrás a nuestras espaldas de esta pizzeria tenemos la galería
维克多·科西奥·曼努埃莱 2 胜利了 曼努埃莱 2
is victor corcio manuele 2 victorious manuele 2
es victorio corcio manuele 2 victorio manuele 2
好吧，停下来！
Okay, stop!
¡Vale, para!
离开，离开，离开。
Leave, leave, leave.
Deja, deja, deja.
你说吧，你说吧。
You say it, you say it.
Decílo vos, decílo vos.
你的不是时尚，你的是食物。
Yours is not fashion, yours is food.
Lo tuyo no es la moda, lo tuyo es la comida.
该画廊名为维托里奥·埃马努埃莱二世。
The gallery is called Vittorio Emanuele II.
La galería se llama Vittorio Emanuele II.
世界的全球震中。
the global epicenter of the world.
el epicentro global del mundo.
奢侈品牌有Louis Vuitton、Prada、Gucci……
There are luxury brands like Louis Vuitton, Prada, Gucci...
Están marcas de lujo como Louis Vuitton, Prada, Gucci...
我要进去买点东西。
And I'm going to go in and buy something.
Y yo vamos a entrar y vamos a comprarnos algo.
包容自己。
Comprise yourselves.
Cúmprate vos.
这对我不起作用。
It doesn't work for me.
A mí no me da.
我们有这样的品牌...
We have brands like...
Tenemos marcas como...
我们有像法拉利这样的品牌，而你看起来太fachini哦，不，令人难以置信的是他如何把我弄傻了，我将手臂举到另一边，他杀了我
We have brands like Ferrari and you look so fachini Oh no, incredible how he threw me stupid, I raised my arm to the other side and he killed me
Tenemos marcas como Ferrari y quedás así de fachini Ay no, increíble cómo me tiró boludo, levanté el brazo para el otro lado y me mató
奢华、优雅、精致……不，是警察！
A luxury, a class, a finesse... No, the police!
Un lujo, una clase, una finura... ¡No, la policía!
好吧，劳蒂，我们来玩一个简短的美食游戏吧。我会给你两顿饭，你必须选择一顿。
Well Lauti, let's play a short, gastronomic game. I'll throw you two meals and you have to choose one.
Bueno Lauti, vamos a hacer un jueguito cortito, gastronómico Te tiro dos comidas y me tenés que elegir una
这就像美食世界杯。
It's like the food world cup.
Es como el mundial de comida.
确切地。
Exactly.
Exactamente.
短且在足部。
Short and at the foot.
Cortito y al pie.
莫雷西村
Moresi village
Chorio Moresi
空香肠或内脏？
Empty chorizo ​​or entrails?
Chorizo Vacío o entraña?
牛排或烤肉的空眼？
Empty eye of steak or roast?
Vacío Ojo de bife o asado?
烤。
Roast.
Asado.
马坦布里托还是邦迪奥拉？
Matambrito or bondiola?
Matambrito o bondiola?
数学。
Mathema.
Matame.
猪肉还是肉？
Pork or meat?
Cerdo o de carne?
猪肉。
Pork.
De cerdo.
那不勒斯，那不勒斯，不是吗？
Neapolitan, Neapolitan, ¿o no?
Neapolítana, Neapolítana, ¿o no?
是的
Yeah
Sí
或者加柠檬。
Or with lemon.
O con limón.
简单也很好。
Simple is fine too.
Simple está bien también.
普罗旺斯柠檬 一点点。
The Provençal lemon a little bit.
El limoncito Provençal un poquitito.
每个人都选择猪肉。
Everyone is choosing the pork one.
Todos están eligiendo el de cerdo.
他们正在管理整头猪吗？
Are they running the whole pig?
¿Están dirigiendo todo el cerdo?
是的，是的，是的，我存钱了，呵呵。
Yes, yes, yes, I bank it, huh.
Sí, sí, sí, lo banco, eh.
猪肉屠夫，羊乳干酪风格。
Pork butchers, Roquefort style.
Matambritos del cerdo, a la Roquefort.
他必须帮助一切。
He has to help everything.
Él le tiene que poner el ayudín a todo.
全部都有一个优点。
All with a plus.
Todo con un plus.
他扩大了一切，扩大了始终完整的组合
He enlarges everything, enlarges the always complete combo
él lo agranda todo, agranda el combo siempre completito
我们就是这样，吃得好，吃得好。
This is how we have it, well eaten, well fed.
Así lo tenemos, bien comidito, bien alimentado.
我不能再吃更多了。
I can't eat more.
No puedo comer más.
典型的西西里奶油甜馅煎饼卷，里面塞满了乳清干酪。
The typical Sicilian cannoli, stuffed with ricotta.
El típico canoli siciliano, relleno de ricotta.
但它是甜的还是咸的？
But is it sweet or salty?
Pero es dulce o salado?
不，是一点点。
No, it's a little bit and a little bit.
No, es un poquito y un poquito.
它有这样的混合口味。
It has like this mixture of flavors.
Tiene como la mezcla así de sabores.
典型的乳清干酪，里面装满了乳清干酪，然后里面有配料，这边有巧克力，这边有开心果
the typical one with ricotta, filled with ricotta and then it has ingredients here you have chocolate on this side and on this side you have pistachio
el típico con ricotta, relleno de ricotta y después tiene ingredientes acá tenés de este lado chocolate y de este lado tenés pistachio
它是混合动力吗？
Is it a hybrid?
¿Es un híbrido?
这是一个混合体。
It's a hybrid.
Es un híbrido.
你能进入这里吗？
Were you able to enter the premises here?
¿Pudiste entrar acá al local?
因为？
Because?
¿Por qué?
因为他是佩菲雷利。
Because it's Peffirelli.
Porque es Peffirelli.
就是这样，佩菲雷利。
There it is, Peffirelli.
Ahí está, Peffirelli.
我们吃饭吧？
Shall we eat?
¿Vamos a comer?
伪装成typesi。
Disguised as typesi.
Disfrazado de tiposi.
这家伙整天都在休息。
All day resting the guy.
Todo el día descansando al tío.
现在我必须像往常一样去付钱。
Now I have to go and pay, as always.
Ahora tengo que ir y pagar, como siempre.
我不会说什么。
I'm not going to say anything.
No voy a decir nada.
我要尝试一下。
I'm going to try.
Voy a probar.
就在那里。
There it is.
Ahí está.
就在那里。
There it is.
Ahí está.
你喜欢吗？
How do you like it?
¿Cómo le gusta?
开心果在巧克力片的另一面和里面
pistacchio on the other side the chocolate chips and inside
pistacchio del otro lado las pepitas de chocolate y adentro
充满乳清干酪，就在那里。
full of ricotta, there it is.
lleno de ricota, ahí está.
它仍然是甜的乳清干酪。
It's still sweet ricotta.
Es ricota dulce igual.
就像蛋糕里面的乳清干酪一样，甜甜的。
It's like the ricotta inside the cake, sweet, sweet.
Es como la ricota dentro de la torta, dulce, dulce.
好的。
Good.
Buenillo.
安德烈，我的祖母。
André, my grandmother.
André, mi abuela.
让他夹在我们中间，每个星期六中午我都会去我奶奶家吃午饭
let him be between us, every Saturday at noon I would go to my grandmother's house for lunch
dejar a estar entre nosotros, yo todos los sábados al mediodía iba a almorzar a la casa de mi abuela
我在布宜诺斯艾利斯的一个地方从他那里买了东西
and I bought from him in a place there in Buenos Aires
y le compraba en un lugar allá en Buenos Aires
6个cannolis，我给他带来了6个cannolis，一份加了焦糖牛奶，一份加了糕点奶油，原来是这样加乳清干酪的。
the 6 cannolis and I brought him the 6 cannolis, one with dulce de leche, one with pastry cream, the original is like this with ricotta.
los 6 cannolis y le llevaba los 6 cannolis, uno de dulce de leche, uno de crema pastelera, el original es así con ricota.
但那里有亲戚，所以我每周六中午都会带他们去卡诺尔。
But there are relatives there, so I take them every Saturday noon in Canole.
pero allá hay parientes, entonces les llevo a todos los mediodías de los sábados en Canole.
这让我想起了我的祖父母，疯狂。
It reminds me of my grandparents, crazy.
Me hace recordar a mis abuelos, una locura.
费基尼去付钱，我去外面等他。
Fichini is going to pay, I'm going outside to wait for him.
Fichini va a pagar, yo me voy afuera a esperarlo.
我希望你带来的东西给我带来惊喜。
I hope you surprise me with what you bring.
Espero que me sorprenda con lo que traigas.
这是一件令人难以置信的事情，总是一样的。
It's an incredible thing, always the same.
Es una cosa increíble, siempre lo mismo.
塔诺斯人的穿衣技巧令人难以置信。
The tanos, how they know how to dress, is incredible.
los tanos, como saben vestirse, es increíble.
因为它们总是很时尚，但是要小心，朋友们。
Because they are always in fashion, but be careful, friends.
Porque siempre están a la moda, pero ojo amiguitos.
我不知道，我们也穿得很好，呵呵。
I don't know, we're also well dressed, huh.
No sé, también estamos bien vestidos, eh.
谢谢你，也谢谢你。
Thanks to you, to you too.
Gracias a vos, a ti también.
为什么？
And why?
¿Y por qué?
因为？
Because?
¿Por qué?
显然，因为你没有看到迪达。
Because you didn't see Dida, obviously.
Porque no viste a Dida, obvio.
煎饼火？
Pancake flames?
Panqueque o flama?
饼子。
Pancake.
Panqueque.
当牛奶，里面。
When milk, inside.
Cuando se leche, adentro.
你们很多人。
Many of you.
Muchos ustedes.
我那里有玉米淀粉 alfajorcito
I have a cornstarch alfajorcito there
Tengo un alfajorcito de maicena ahí
半月还是阿尔法霍尔？
Half moon or alfajores?
Meia luna o alfajores?
。
.
Meia luna.
继续努力吧？
Keep it up?
Manteca o orasa?
黄油。
Butter.
Manteca.
油炸还是烤米兰？
Fried or baked Milanese?
¿Milanesa frita o al horno?
薯条。
Fries.
Frita.
我喜欢它让所有的墙壁都回到你的触摸中，公牛不会犹豫一秒钟
I like that it returns all the walls to your touch, the bull does not hesitate for a second
me gusta que te devuelve todas las paredes al toque, no duda un segundo el toro
你知道吗，朋友？
You know, friend?
¿Sabes, amigo?
这个东西要花我多少钱……是的，Valoro，这是一个谎言。
How expensive this one is costing me... Yes, Valoro, it's a lie.
Lo caro que me está saliendo este... Sí, Valoro, es mentira.
很好，但如果你多加小心的话，也能干，烤的，习惯的，但油炸的。
And good, but capable if you take a little more care, baked, customary, but fried.
Y bueno, pero capaz si te cuidas un poquito más al horno, costumbre, pero frita.
不，我们在这里说的是我喜欢什么，然后是我吃什么，还有别的。
No, here we are saying what I like, then what I eat, something else.
No, acá estamos diciendo lo que me gusta, después lo que como, otra cosa.
完美的。
Perfect.
Perfecto.
这一切都像什么都没有一样。
All of that is like nothing.
Todo eso no como nada.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我愿意。
I do.
Yo sí.
我是甜心，是守望者还是冰淇淋？
What am I sweet, a watchman or ice cream?
¿Qué soy dulce, un vigilante o helado?
会员还是土豆？
Member or potato?
¿Membrillo o batata?
柑橘我不喜欢
Quince I don't like it
Membrillo No me gusta
我不喜欢唯一的名字。
I don't like the only name.
No me gusta el único nombre.
去吃冰淇淋吧，呵呵。
To the ice cream, huh.
Al helado, eh.
是的，房间很小。
Yes, little room.
Sí, cuartito.
哇，我的口水都流下来了。
Wow, my mouth is watering.
Uy, se me hace agua la boca.
你可知道？
Did you know?
¿Sabes qué?
不不不，我什么都喜欢。
No, no, I like everything.
No, no, me gusta todo.
是的，这里的一切，你知道吗？
Yes, everything here, you know what?
Sí, acá todo, ¿sabés qué?
我真的很喜欢这里的开心果。
I really like pistachio here.
De pistachio me gusta mucho acá.
还有甜饼干或咸饼干？
And sweet or savory biscuits?
Y bizcochitos dulces o salados?
我不喜欢饼干。
I don't like biscuits.
No me gustan bizcochitos.
别把手放在上面，就没事了。嘿，我们吃炸披萨吧，朋友，我从来没有吃过炸披萨。
Don't put your hand on it, you're fine. Hey, let's eat fried pizza, friend, I've never had fried pizza.
no te pongas la mano, estas muy bien eh vamos a comer pizza frita amigo nunca me había comido pizza frita
那里有一个摄像头，可以显示他们目前如何制作披萨。
There is a camera there that shows how they make the pizza at the moment.
Hay una cámara ahí que muestra cómo hacen la pizza en el momento.
太不可思议了。
It's incredible.
Es increíble.
我一生中从未见过这种情况。
I've never seen that in my life.
Eso no lo vi nunca en mi vida.
对于那些不知道的人来说，炸披萨就像卡尔松 (calzón)。
Fried pizza, for those who don't know, is like a calzón.
La pizza frita, para el que no sabe, es como un calzón.
是的，我刚刚看到了。
Yes, I just saw it.
Sí, la acabo de ver.
我以为这是披萨，但是……
I thought it was a pizza, but...
Yo pensé que era una pizza, pero...
每个人都拿着一个巨大的肉馅卷饼，裹在内衣里。
Everyone comes out with a huge empanada closed in their underwear.
Todos salen con una empanada enorme cerrada en calzón.
想象一下...
Imagine that...
Imagínate que...
我和你的想法是一样的，但是你仔细想想，你是怎么做到的呢？
I thought the same as you, but if you think about it, how do you do it?
Yo pensaba lo mismo que vos, pero si te pones a pensar, ¿cómo haces?
如果炸好的披萨没有像内裤一样封闭，该如何清洗呢？
If the fried pizza is not closed like a panty, how do you clean it?
Si la pizza frita no es cerrada como un calzón, cómo la fregues?
让她陷入掠夺者之中是不可能的。
It is impossible to get her into a predator.
Es imposible meterla en un apredador.
这是不可能的。
It's impossible.
Es imposible.
我会一如既往地用 Visa 付款，瞧。
I'm going to pay with Visa as always, look.
Voy a pagar con Visa como siempre, mira.
萨拉米香肠，沙拉。
Salami, salad.
Salame, salada.
谢谢。
Gracias.
我可以告诉你一件事吗？
Can I tell you something?
¿Te puedo decir algo?
是的，它弯曲了。
Yes, it bends.
Sí, se dobla.
它弯曲了。
It bends.
Se dobla.
当然，因为你必须吃馅料。
Of course, because you have to eat the filling.
Claro, porque tenés que comer el relleno.
确切地。
Exactly.
Exactamente.
抓住你的，就在这里，我们把它包起来一点，哦，这有多危险
grab yours, here it goes, we wrap it up a little, oh how dangerous this is
agarrá tuya, ahí va, la envolvemos un poquito, uy que peligro esto
好吧，抓住这里。
Well, grab it here.
Pues agarrás acá.
我怎么知道表是什么？
How do I know what the table is?
¿Cómo se que es la mesa?
不，不，我猜是桌子。
No, no, I guess it's the table.
No, no, supongo que es la mesa.
就是蔬菜那一类。
That's the vegetable one.
Esa es la de verdura.
那个小女孩，她到底长啥样？
The little girl, what was she like?
La recoleta, ¿cómo era?
蜗牛 蜗牛 recolita
the escarole the escarole recolita
la escarola la escarola recolita
他从来没有在盘子里见过生菜叶，这家伙只是汉堡包，没有别的，像我祖父一样的蜗牛
He never saw a lettuce leaf on a plate, the guy is hamburgers and nothing else, escarole like my grandfather
nunca vio una hoja de lechuga en un plato, el tipo es hamburguesas y nada más, la escarola como mi abuelo
烤肉怎么样？
How is it with the roast?
¿Cómo está con el asado?
非常好。
Very good.
Muy bien.
吐？
Spit?
¿Asador?
吐。
Spit.
Asador.
看起来。
It looks.
Tiene pinta.
该俱乐部可容纳 70 人。
The club for 70 people.
El club para 70 personas.
你有油漆或烧焦吗？
Do you have paint or burnt?
¿Tienes pinta o quemado?
不，是手。
No, the hands.
No, las manos.
没关系，没关系。
It's okay, it's okay.
Está bien, está bien.
我有视频所以...是的，是的。
I have video so... Yes, yes.
Tengo video para que... Sí, sí.
烧烤时的装饰。
Garnish for a barbecue.
Guarrición para un asado.
油炸、捣碎、沙拉。
Fried, mashed, salad.
Frita, puré, ensalada.
我问。
I asked.
Pregunté.
好吧，亚历克西斯说肉加肉，法库说……
Well, Alexis said meat with meat, Facu said...
Bueno, Alexis dijo carne con carne, Facu dijo...
俄罗斯沙拉？
Russian salad?
¿Ensalada rusa?
俄罗斯沙拉！
Russian salad!
¡Ensalada rusa!
你想要什么？
What do you want?
¿Qué querés?
多么女王啊！
What a queen!
¡Qué quenino!
他很矛盾。
He's conflicted.
Está confrito.
是的，但这就是菊苣。
Yes, but that's the endive.
Sí, pero esa es la escarola.
这是菊苣。
This is endive.
Esta es escarola.
来吧，你先走。
Come on, you go first.
Dale, andá vos primero.
看看你吃得好不好。
Let's see if you eat it well.
A ver si lo comes bien.
滴，滴，滴。
Drip, drip, drip.
Chorrea, chorrea, chorrea.
很重。
Very heavy.
Muy pesada.
服下药丸。
Take the pill.
Tomate la pastilla.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
很重。
Very heavy.
Muy pesada.
那是最多的音符……是的！
That's the note with the most... Yes!
Esa es la nota con más... ¡Sí!
那个看起来很饱，不，不。
That one looks stuffed, no, no.
Esa se la nota con relleno, no, no.
我开始在这里寻找填充物。
I'm starting to find the filling here.
Estoy empezando a encontrar el relleno acá.
这是配番茄酱的。
This is with pomodoro sauce.
Esta es con salsa pomorodo.
番茄钟。
Pomodoro.
Pomorodo.
谢天谢地，你不是一个有影响力的人，呵呵。
Thank goodness you're not an influencer, huh.
Menos mal que no sos influencer, eh.
伙计们，我是一位美食影响者。
I'm a food influencer, guys.
Soy influencer de comida, chicos.
但不要使用奶酪，但面团是非常薄的油炸披萨面团，不，这并不令人难以置信
but don't use the cheese but the dough is a very thin fried pizza dough no it's not incredible
pero no enganche el quesito pero la masa es una masa de pizza bien finita frita no no es increíble
你为什么给我蔬菜？
Why do you give me vegetables?
¿Por qué me das verdura?
你对我说什么，胖子？
What do you say to me, fat man?
¿Qué me decís, gordo?
是的，但我希望我们改变一点，白痴，因为这里是集体的，就是这样。
Yes, but I want us to change a little, idiot, because here this is collective, this is how it is.
Sí, pero quiero que cambiemos un poco, boludo, porque acá esto es colectivo, esto es así.
让我们看看，这真是一团糟，很恶心，但是，嘿，这就是我们来的目的。
Let's see, this is a beautiful mess, it's disgusting, but hey, that's what we came for.
A ver, esto es un enchastre hermoso, es un asco, pero bueno, a eso vinimos.
如果他们知道我是怎么来的，为什么还要带我来，对​​吧？
Why do they bring me if they know how I get, right?
Para qué me traen si saben cómo me pongo, ¿no?
是卡罗尔。
It's Carol.
Es carola.
这是炸蔬菜馅饼，这个。
It's a fried vegetable pie, this.
Es una tarta de verduras fritas, esto.
仪式，??h？
Riteral, ¿h?
Riteral, ¿eh?
全部的。
Total.
你有迷你帕特里吗？
Do you have a minipatri?
¿Tiene un minipatri?
米兰大教堂 我在心里画十字，因为我感觉……胆固醇进入了井，然后它就消失了……看看它是如何打开的……
Milano's duomo I cross myself because I feel like... cholesterol to the well and it's gone... look how it's open...
el duomo de milano me persigno porque siento que... colesterol a la well y se me va... mira como está abierta...
它的顶部和底部都是开放的。
It is open at the top and bottom.
Esta abierta arriba y abajo.
听着，我要从这里咬他。
Look, I'm going to bite him from here.
Mira, de acá lo voy a morder.
这是萨拉米香肠。
This is the salami one.
Esta es la de salame.
我们走吧？
Shall we go?
¿Vamos?
光是看着就让我饿了。
It made me hungry just looking at it.
Me dio hambre tan solo verlo.
面团非常好，就像他们这样炸的。
The dough is very good, just like they fried it like this.
La masa está muy bien, igual que la han frita así.
但它很重。
But it is very heavy.
Pero es muy pesada.
你有意大利乳清干酪吗？
Do you have ricotta?
¿Tiene ricota?
它有乳清干酪。
It has ricotta.
Tiene ricota.
它有乳清干酪，有萨拉米香肠。
It has ricotta, it has salami.
Tiene ricota, tiene salame.
你怎么知道这个？
How do you know this?
¿Cómo sabés esto?
它已经发生了，我自动地看到了......我感到高兴的是......
It has and I see and automatically... What I'm happy about is that...
Tiene y yo veo y automáticamente... De lo que estoy contento es que...
这种时尚完好无损。
this fashion intact.
intacto esta moda.
最好的，不可思议。
The best, incredible.
La mejor, increíble.
我可以展示一些东西吗？
Can I show something?
¿Puedo mostrar algo?
餐巾纸的尺寸。
The size of the napkin.
El tamaño de la servilleta.
我告诉你，选择合适的尺寸，这样就不会弄脏。
Go for the size so you don't get stains, I tell you.
Ve el tamaño para que no te manches, yo te digo.
这不是节日里的萨拉米香肠，而是小方块、立方体里的萨拉米香肠。
It's not salami in fetes, it's like salami in little squares, cubes.
No es salame en fetes, es como salame en cuadraditos, cubitos.
莱科是最富有的，这对其他两人来说似乎很正常。
Leco is this the richest, it seemed normal to the other two.
Leco es esta la más rica, a las otras dos me pareció normal.
这个更好，事实是我给这个一个八分，我给其他一个六分。
This one is superior, the truth is that I give this one an eight, I give the others a six.
Esta está superior, la verdad que a esta le doy un ocho, a las otras le doy un seis.
回来了。
It's back.
Ya se la vuelve.
以免玷污自己。
So as not to stain myself.
Para no mancharme.
而且你没有问饮料。
And you didn't ask about drinks.
Y de bebida no preguntaste.
你打开它，我不会为你安装任何东西，不尊重，我会打开它。
You open it, I'm not going to install any of that for you, no respect, I'll open it.
Abrilo vos, nada de eso te voy a instalar ni respetuos, abrilo yo.
噢，难以置信。
Oh, incredible.
Oh, increíble.
嘿，奥迪适合多少钱？
Hey, how much does the Audi fit?
Che, ¿cuánto calza la Audi?
43岁半。
43 and a half.
43 y medio.
经过前面的诱捕峡谷。
After the trapping ravine ahead.
Después barranco de atrapa adelante.
或者反过来。
or the other way around.
o al revés.
我喜欢它，因为每个人都认真对待它。
I like it because everyone takes it seriously.
Me gusta porque todos se lo toman en serio.
太不可思议了。
It's incredible.
Es increíble.